{
	"Cards": [
		{
			"Answer": 1,
			"Question": "1*1",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 2,
			"Question": "1*2",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 3,
			"Question": "1*3",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 4,
			"Question": "1*4",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 5,
			"Question": "1*5",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 6,
			"Question": "1*6",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 7,
			"Question": "1*7",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 8,
			"Question": "1*8",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 9,
			"Question": "1*9",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 10,
			"Question": "1*10",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 11,
			"Question": "1*11",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 12,
			"Question": "1*12",
			"Tags": [
				"1s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 2,
			"Question": "2*1",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 4,
			"Question": "2*2",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 6,
			"Question": "2*3",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 8,
			"Question": "2*4",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 10,
			"Question": "2*5",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 12,
			"Question": "2*6",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 14,
			"Question": "2*7",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 16,
			"Question": "2*8",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 18,
			"Question": "2*9",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 20,
			"Question": "2*10",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 22,
			"Question": "2*11",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 24,
			"Question": "2*12",
			"Tags": [
				"2s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 3,
			"Question": "3*1",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 6,
			"Question": "3*2",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 9,
			"Question": "3*3",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 12,
			"Question": "3*4",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 15,
			"Question": "3*5",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 18,
			"Question": "3*6",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 21,
			"Question": "3*7",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 24,
			"Question": "3*8",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 27,
			"Question": "3*9",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 30,
			"Question": "3*10",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 33,
			"Question": "3*11",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 36,
			"Question": "3*12",
			"Tags": [
				"3s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 4,
			"Question": "4*1",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 8,
			"Question": "4*2",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 12,
			"Question": "4*3",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 16,
			"Question": "4*4",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 20,
			"Question": "4*5",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 24,
			"Question": "4*6",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 28,
			"Question": "4*7",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 32,
			"Question": "4*8",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 36,
			"Question": "4*9",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 40,
			"Question": "4*10",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 44,
			"Question": "4*11",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 48,
			"Question": "4*12",
			"Tags": [
				"4s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 5,
			"Question": "5*1",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 10,
			"Question": "5*2",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 15,
			"Question": "5*3",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 20,
			"Question": "5*4",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 25,
			"Question": "5*5",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 30,
			"Question": "5*6",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 35,
			"Question": "5*7",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 40,
			"Question": "5*8",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 45,
			"Question": "5*9",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 50,
			"Question": "5*10",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 55,
			"Question": "5*11",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 60,
			"Question": "5*12",
			"Tags": [
				"5s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 6,
			"Question": "6*1",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 12,
			"Question": "6*2",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 18,
			"Question": "6*3",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 24,
			"Question": "6*4",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 30,
			"Question": "6*5",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 36,
			"Question": "6*6",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 42,
			"Question": "6*7",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 48,
			"Question": "6*8",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 54,
			"Question": "6*9",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 60,
			"Question": "6*10",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 66,
			"Question": "6*11",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 72,
			"Question": "6*12",
			"Tags": [
				"6s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 7,
			"Question": "7*1",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 14,
			"Question": "7*2",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 21,
			"Question": "7*3",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 28,
			"Question": "7*4",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 35,
			"Question": "7*5",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 42,
			"Question": "7*6",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 49,
			"Question": "7*7",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 56,
			"Question": "7*8",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 63,
			"Question": "7*9",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 70,
			"Question": "7*10",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 77,
			"Question": "7*11",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 84,
			"Question": "7*12",
			"Tags": [
				"7s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 8,
			"Question": "8*1",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 16,
			"Question": "8*2",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 24,
			"Question": "8*3",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 32,
			"Question": "8*4",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 40,
			"Question": "8*5",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 48,
			"Question": "8*6",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 56,
			"Question": "8*7",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 64,
			"Question": "8*8",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 72,
			"Question": "8*9",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 80,
			"Question": "8*10",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 88,
			"Question": "8*11",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 96,
			"Question": "8*12",
			"Tags": [
				"8s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 9,
			"Question": "9*1",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 18,
			"Question": "9*2",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 27,
			"Question": "9*3",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 36,
			"Question": "9*4",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 45,
			"Question": "9*5",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 54,
			"Question": "9*6",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 63,
			"Question": "9*7",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 72,
			"Question": "9*8",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 81,
			"Question": "9*9",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 90,
			"Question": "9*10",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 99,
			"Question": "9*11",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 108,
			"Question": "9*12",
			"Tags": [
				"9s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 10,
			"Question": "10*1",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 20,
			"Question": "10*2",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 30,
			"Question": "10*3",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 40,
			"Question": "10*4",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 50,
			"Question": "10*5",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 60,
			"Question": "10*6",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 70,
			"Question": "10*7",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 80,
			"Question": "10*8",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 90,
			"Question": "10*9",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 100,
			"Question": "10*10",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 110,
			"Question": "10*11",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 120,
			"Question": "10*12",
			"Tags": [
				"10s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 11,
			"Question": "11*1",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 22,
			"Question": "11*2",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 33,
			"Question": "11*3",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 44,
			"Question": "11*4",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 55,
			"Question": "11*5",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 66,
			"Question": "11*6",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 77,
			"Question": "11*7",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 88,
			"Question": "11*8",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 99,
			"Question": "11*9",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 110,
			"Question": "11*10",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 121,
			"Question": "11*11",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 132,
			"Question": "11*12",
			"Tags": [
				"11s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 12,
			"Question": "12*1",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"1s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 24,
			"Question": "12*2",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"2s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 36,
			"Question": "12*3",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"3s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 48,
			"Question": "12*4",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"4s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 60,
			"Question": "12*5",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"5s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 72,
			"Question": "12*6",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"6s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 84,
			"Question": "12*7",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"7s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 96,
			"Question": "12*8",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"8s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 108,
			"Question": "12*9",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"9s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 120,
			"Question": "12*10",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"10s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 132,
			"Question": "12*11",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"11s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		},
		{
			"Answer": 144,
			"Question": "12*12",
			"Tags": [
				"12s",
				"12s"
			],
			"Type": "number"
		}
	]
}
